deepbox.com 2010-12-29

# 2.0 Layouts, Myspace 2.0 Layouts, Myspace Layouts, Myspace Comments, Funny Myspace Comments, Myspace 3.0 Layouts

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the personal information that we collect and receive. We do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under 13, unless we believe such collection to be permitted by law. Our policy with respect to children under 13 is described below. 

Overview

We gather user information to provide you with a customized experience on our site. Your user information helps us tailor the content, services, goods and advertising to your viewing preferences. So, we may ask you to register and provide personal information when you post comments or utilize other areas of our site. However, you always have the right to choose not to register or provide personal information, in which case you may not have access to those areas. 

If you choose to register with our site, from time to time we may e-mail you with messages about our services or third party products and services we believe may be of interest to you, such as new products, features, services, and updated information. Our newsletters may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the newsletters, including whether you opened the e-mail and what links (if any) were clicked. We use that information exclusively to improve your site experience. If you choose to register with our site you may automatically receive e-mails to confirm your registration and to provide you with necessary information relating to the access or use of your registration. With the exception of the e-mails described in the preceding sentence which are necessary to provide customer support and deliver products and services to you, you may opt-out of receiving e-mail from us as described below. 

Use of Information

When you register, we ask for your e-mail address, a unique user name selected by you and other information. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and may be able to provide additional preferential information. 

We may use such personally identifiable information to provide the information or content you have to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested (such as future promotional materials), or for other purposes disclosed from time to time. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our Web Site or changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Web Site. In addition, we may use information collected to improve the content and navigation of our Web Site, or for other internal purposes. 

Communications on the Internet take place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address that any connection is made from and we may use these IP addresses to help diagnose and resolve technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. 

Cookies

Deepbox may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Website, including to operate and improve offerings through the Website; to help us to authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Website; to remember your preferences and registration information; and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you. Deepbox does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Website may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. 

Our Website contains links, including banner and other ads, to other Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

Third Party Ad Servers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Sharing Information

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties. However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone.s safety. 

We may request demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection or we have your permission. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only. 

Opting-Out

If you provide us with your e-mail address, and do not opt-out of receiving e-mail from us, we may e-mail you with information, including information about selected third parties. If you do not want to receive information from us, you may decline to receive it (or Opt-Out) either when you provide personal information to us or you may update your profile. You may also choose to Opt-Out from certain types of e-mail by following the unsubscribe instructions that appear on such e-mails. You may also contact us as provided below. Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to opt-out and when it is processed and reflected in our systems; accordingly you might continue to receive e-mails from us for a few days after you unsubscribe. Additional information regarding opting out of network advertising is located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. We maintain records of those users who opt-out of specific e-mail options so that we do not e-mail them with respect to those types of e-mails 

Children Under 13

Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we are committed to complying with the Children.s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). On those areas of the sites that ask for age, we do not collect personal information from individuals who identify themselves as under the age of 13, except in limited circumstances where we believe that such collection is permitted under COPPA. 

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail, as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. 

Additional Information

We have implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. If a user elects to use our site for informing a friend about our site or particular features or content, we ask them for the friend.s name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. 

Your personal information is password-protected, and you should always take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, always remember to sign out and close your browser window when you exit the site to prevent others from accessing your personal information. 

We maintain archives of our web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from our active database (see above regarding web logs). These archives are maintained for data recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes. 

If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, be advised we are based in the United States and your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not be the same as in other parts of the world. By using the site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

Maintaining Your Profile

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of your user profile by notifying us when you change your address, phone number or e-mail address. You may, at any time, update your information or stop receiving communication from us, by signing in and and making the appropriate changes. 

Contact Information

Please address comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy to us via email to: 

Staff [@] deepbox.com 

Binding Agreement

Use of our site is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

Revised 12/10/09.
